<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CrimeManagement</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_exit">Exit</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">
        What about this application? \n
        In this application uses two catagory.\n
        1.User modiul\n
        2.Admin modiul\n
        User modiul :- In this section user will get a login state if has no account in this
        application he can do sign up first then he can easily can go to the report page\n
        And then he can report easily to this section \n
        this apps also has been given to the user if one crime report seem wrong then he/she modify
        or edit this report and can sent this to the admin\n\n
        Admin Modiul :- In this section Admin have an special email pass only for see them
        and when the admin seems any crime report is true then he will go for action\n
        And he has given a opportunity for three update session\n
        (i).seen :--> first time he see that...\n
        (ii)processing : when he process about any report.\n
        (iii) finish : Or work has done by successfully.\n\n
        In this application easily and low costing way we can report our
        authority or corporation managment system.\n
        Who are the user of this app?\n
        This application basically can used everyone can be victim or any genourlist or any
        goverment forces. In a word everyone use this app.\n
         Why this application is needed for us?\n
        In this application developer or creator created in two catagory One is user and 2nd is
        admin\n
        Basicaly we can see when a affacted people or victim of crime harrage or hamper by
        the smuggling and criminal then he/she does not know what should they do or
        what will they do imidiately but if they have a smart phone and this app
        then they can easily report nearest pollice station for helping them and easily
        they can overcome their haragement\n
        Admin, how can help the victim of who have got into trouble ?\n
        In this application uses two catagories Admin modiul is one of them
        Admin can see who has sent report and who are the victim
        then he first justify it its real or not if this report is real then he action imedieately\n
        thus this way one victim can get better help\

       </string>
</resources>
